arbitron.com 2001-02-28

# Arbitron Privacy Statement

THE ARBITRON COMPANY'S WEB SITE PRIVACY STATEMENT

The Arbitron Company is a media research firm that provides information services used by the media, their advertisers and advertising agencies to develop local marketing strategies. Consistent with our corporate values of honesty, integrity and trust, Arbitron is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information. In order to understand the manner in which Arbitron protects information provided to us via the Web site, please read the following Privacy Statement for the Web site. 

VISITORS

Visitors may access Arbitron's Web site and browse to review the services Arbitron offers without providing personal information. 

ARBITRON'S SUBSCRIBERS/CLIENTS

Arbitron collects personally identifiable information, or personal information, such as name, organization, address, business and personal e-mail addresses, and telephone number, when our clients provide this information at the time of registration. Clients may also be asked a few short questions about the computers, software, and Internet systems their organizations use. **This information is shared internally at Arbitron to the extent necessary to ensure data security and to complete a client order**. We do not rent, sell or market personal data about our clients to third parties. 

In some instances, we may use other companies to perform certain services on our behalf. These companies may need access to personal information to complete the services. The companies will not have authorization to use personally-identifiable information for purposes other than to perform the services on our behalf. The data we collect are considered our proprietary business assets and may be transferred if Arbitron or substantially all of its assets are acquired by another company. We may also be required by law to release personally-identifiable information under certain circumstances. 

Arbitron's subscribers are reminded that all Arbitron diarykeeper information is confidential and used under the guidelines set forth by the Media Rating Council. 

CHILDREN

Arbitron does not knowingly solicit information from children on this Web site or knowingly market its services to children. Arbitron conducts research with children, in on-line venues other than this Web site, in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. 

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED AUTOMATICALLY

As mentioned above, for general browsing and looking at our Web site's offerings, no personal information is captured. Arbitron does obtain certain information each time a visitor logs onto the Web site. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser being used, the type of computer operating system being used and the domain name of the Web site from which the visitor linked to our site. 

COOKIES

When a visitor or client views Arbitron's Web site, we may store some information on the viewer's computer's hard drive. This information will be in the form of a "cookie" or similar file and can help us in many ways. For example, cookies allow us to track data for service reports and to read the database and present it back to the user. With most Internet browsers, you may erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. If you are a client, should you choose to block or delete cookies, you will have difficulty accessing Arbitron's proprietary information. 

SECURITY

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, Arbitron implements procedures to safeguard and secure the information that is collected online. Although Arbitron will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of the information provided, transmissions made by means of the Internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Arbitron is not liable for disclosure of the information supplied due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties. 

UNITED STATES CLIENTS

The Arbitron Company's Privacy Statement is currently limited only to our United States clients and visitors to our Web site. A privacy statement will be developed in the future for our Web site for our international audiences, which will comply with local laws or customs where Arbitron conducts business. 

E-MAIL

Arbitron may use the e-mail addresses provided at registration to send e-mails concerning updates or announcements about our services to our subscribers. You may indicate on the subscriber registration form that you do not wish to receive e-mail information from Arbitron. 

CONTACT INFORMATION

Arbitron reserves the right to contact our clients regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement, privacy policy, or any other polices or agreements relevant to our clients.

If you would like to review and/or update the client information that you provided at registration, or if there are any questions or concerns about the privacy policy, please send us an e-mail at _[webprivacy@arbitron.com.](mailto:webprivacy@arbitron.com)_

 __

Be sure to reread this Privacy Statement occasionally to note any updates. 

Last revised 12/00

Home

Copyright © 2001 by The Arbitron Company
